spinnakerboutique.it 2017-12-10

# Privacy notice | Spinnaker Boutique

You do not have to give us any personal data in order to use most of our Website. However, if you wish to send us a message or chat online, receive our newsletter and special offers via email or order products and services, you will need to provide certain information to us. This may include your name, address or location, phone number and email address and when using our contact form, your message and any other information you wish to provide to us. 

Please note that in order to order products or services, you will need to register an account with us.   
We ask for your phone number to allow us to process your order and to let you know the status of your order. This number may be given to our courier for delivery services in order for us to keep you informed. You may also choose to provide your date of birth and gender in order to provide you with a more personalised shopping experience. 

Please note we do not keep your payment card details on file. We use third party providers, including PayPal, to process payments, and only these entities see your payment card details. 

We also keep a record of the purchases you make from any of our partner boutiques. This means that we can help to deal more quickly with any queries or problems you may have and also to ensure that any information that we send you is relevant. 

When you visit our Website, we also automatically collect certain information from you. For more information about this, please see the "Cookies and other tracking technologies" section below.

####   The information we collect allows us to:

  * Provide the products and services you have ordered;
  * To verify your identity and details of your payment method or credit card account;
  * Administer our Website and provide customer services;
  * Plan and manage our commercial business activities including analysis of your shopping habits, product and style preferences;
  * Communicate with you (including via email or telephone where such contact details have been provided);
  * Tell you about our offers, services or products;

You agree that we may disclose your personal data to other companies within the Spinnaker group (listed on our Website) and to our and their service providers and agents for the above purposes. This will be done confidentially and only to the extent permitted under applicable data protection laws. Such service providers and agents may include without limitation, third parties who carry out customer service, payment processing services, identify verification and fraud management services, hosting and website maintenance. 

We may also release account and other personal information where it is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, safety of Spinnaker.com Limited, our users or others. 

This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for identity verification and fraud protection purposes to the extent permitted by applicable laws. In particular, when you make a purchase from the Website, where we may make searches about you at credit reference agencies for such purposes. The agencies will record details of any search. This information may be used by other subscribers for similar purposes. 

If we sell all or part of our business, or make a sale or transfer of assets, including a sale in bankruptcy or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, we may transfer your personal data to a third party as part of that transaction. 

We may disclose aggregate, anonymised statistics about the number of visitors to our Website or number of purchases made to third parties including our investors.

####   Transfers of your personal data

Your personal information may be transferred to, and stored at a destination outside of the European Economic Area including the US. Such processing may be required in order to fulfil your order, process your payment details or provide support services.

#####   Communication & Marketing

To subscribe to our newsletter containing information about new products, services, features and events from us and our partner boutiques and to receive special offers via email, or telephone, please complete our subscription form. If you make a purchase on our Website, we may also use your details to email you our newsletter and to tell you about our special offers from time to time. 

Please note that any telephone or email communications will only be made by us. We do not sell or otherwise pass your details to third parties for marketing purposes. You can opt-out of these communications at any time via the Unsubscribe link on any email.
